macbooty.com 2010-05-12

# Privacy Statement

We are committed to protecting your privacy when you use this website. In this policy we explain our use of information, what we do with it and what controls you have over our use of it.

From time to time, we add or change functions, features or products to our Web Sites or add or change Services. This, and our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this Privacy Policy. As a result, please remember to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly to review any amendments. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy please don't hesitate to contact us.

### What data do we collect and how do we use it?

**We do not collect or store any information about you personally or as an individual, other than any information that you choose to send us via email or our Contact page.**

###  Log files/IP addresses

When you visit our Web Sites, we automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognised by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer our Web Sites and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.

### Non-personal information

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to our Web Sites. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on our Web Sites. We may from time to time supply the owners or operators of third party sites from which it is possible to link to our Web Sites with information relating to the number of users linking to our Web Sites from their sites. You cannot be identified from this information.

### Use of Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web Site transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. 

**We do not use cookies on this website.**

### Third Parties

This Web Site contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, we suggest that you read their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites. 

We will only sell or rent your personal information to a third party either as part of a sale of the assets of a company name company or having ensured that steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

### Further Information / Comments

It is very important to us that we provide you with the highest level of service. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or any other aspect of our service, please don't hesitate to contact us.
